Guide to the JDub Records Archive 2001-2011 MSS.330
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Original Media
  This series contains non-professionally produced media, mostly demo CDs submitted to JDub Records.
  Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Subseries A: Media
    - 21st Century Girl, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0001)
    - Abraham Inc., 2008 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0002)
    - Adam - "Rasta Say", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0003)
    - Adama - "Mix 1", 2005 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0004)
    - Adonai and I - "Feast of the Passover" dry mixes, 2009 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0005)
    - Afropop Worldwide - "Around the World" and "Hip Deep", 2004 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0006)
    - Afro-Semitic Experience - "Plea for Peace", 2005 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0007)
    - Alan Cohen Experience - "Revolutions", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0008)
    - Alan Cohen and 12 Tribes Band - "Riddim'tion", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0009)
    - Amitai, Sharron Topper, 2010 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0010)
    - Anakronic Electro Orkestra - "Original Nign feat. So Called and Mangu", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0011)
    - Applebaum, Talia - "Flashed in the Darkness", 2006 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0012)
    - Architects of Sound - "Better than Radio", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0013)
    - Areddy, Hadara Levin, 2010 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0014)
    - Aviva - "Songs for Carmen", 2006 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0015)
    - Axum - unmastered, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0016)
    - Baby Bro, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0017)
    - The Baker Brothers, 2010 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0018)
    - Balkan Beat Box - ASRA - Cafe Du Nord, San Francisco, 2005 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0019)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Beno, 2007 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0020)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Bonnaroo, 2006 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0021)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Demo, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0022)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Israeli master, 2003 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0023)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Master, clean, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0024)
    - Balkan Beat Box - re-mix, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0025)
    - Balkan Beat Box - remix, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0026)
    - Balkan Beat Box - remixes, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0027)
    - Balkan Beat Box - single files - "Digital Monkey", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0028)
    - Balkan Beat Box - single files - "Mexico City", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0029)
    - Balkan Beat Box - single files - "Yala Min Zaman", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0030)
    - Base and Brass, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0076)
    - Bashaan, Amit - "System Restore" (copy 1), Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0031)
    - Bashaan, Amit - "System Restore" (copy 2), Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0032)
    - Basya - "Traditional Project", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0033)
    - [Basya], Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0034)
    - Ben - "Live at Tonic", 2003 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0035)
    - Ben & Liat, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0036)
    - The Bentchers, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0037)
    - Betzalel, Einat & Boukhit, Hakim - "Sweeterland", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0038)
    - Betzalel, Noah ben - "Leaving Egypt", 2008 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0039)
    - Beyond the Book, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0040)
    - Beyond Eden - demo, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0041)
    - Big Lazy - "Postcards from X", 2005 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0042)
    - Billet, Asaf - "Design that Goes to 11", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0043)
    - Blume, Danny - "Teeth of Gold", 2002 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0044)
    - Boat CD - JDub and random hip-hop, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0045)
    - Bouzaglou, David, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0046)
    - Breitman, Seth, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0047)
    - Brimstone 127, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0048)
    - Bris, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0049)
    - Burson, Clare - "6 Points demo", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0050)
    - The Camps, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0051)
    - Can Can - "Masters & Healers", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0052)
    - CB Bonus, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0053)
    - Chesed, Yaakov - "Acoustic Sessions", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0054)
    - Chesed, Yaakov - "[Chasdei Hashom]", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0055)
    - Chouva Rap - vol. 1 demo, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0056)
    - Cohen, Zen - "The Flood", 2006 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0057)
    - Conjoin - "Long Live the King!", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0058)
    - Coolooloosh - Demo (copy 1), 2006 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0059)
    - Coolooloosh - Demo (copy 2), 2006 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0060)
    - C-Tre. Flowz and Sino, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0061)
    - Curly Oxide, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0062)
    - Dafna, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0063)
    - Daniel Kahn & The Painted Bird - "Partisans & Parasites", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0077)
    - Dasan, Akil - "A Sampler" (copy 1), Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0064)
    - Dasan, Akil - "A Sampler" (copy 2), Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0065)
    - Dasan, Akil - "The Music of Akil Dasan", 2002 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0066)
    - DeLeon - "Celebrate Brooklyn", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0067)
    - DeLeon - Demos, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0068)
    - DJ Realeyes - "End of the Day: Lounge", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0069)
    - DJ Shotnez - Balkan Beat Box Demo, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0070)
    - DJ Shotnez - mixtape, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0071)
    - DJ Shotnez - Natasha [Matardot], Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0072)
    - DJ Shotnez - Nov, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0073)
    - DJ Shotnez - Rough, no sequence, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0074)
    - DJ Shotnez - Rough, no sequence, untested, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0075)
    - Dreiblatt, Ian, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0078)
    - Duchampion - demo, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0079)
    - Dujov, Simja, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0080)
    - Durousseau, Deni - "The Demimonde", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0081)
    - Dveykes - "Yale Strom", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0082)
    - Eden - "Live EP", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0083)
    - Eilat, Yoni, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0084)
    - Electric Simcha, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0085)
    - Emunah - EP3, 2005 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0086)
    - Eric Blowtorch Plays Himself, 2007 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0087)
    - Eshy - "Attention Deficit Disorder", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0088)
    - Failure is Not an Option - "No Games Involved", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0089)
    - Fastow, Fredric - "Compositions I", 2007 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0090)
    - Fayvish - "At Alpakaclub", 2006 (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0091)
    - Feiner, Corie - "Performance Poet", Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0092)
    - Fishel, Artie and Promised Band, Undated (Box 17, Disk ID: 330.0093)
    - Flya, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0094)
    - Folklezmer - "Puppet Theatre Show", Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0095)
    - Fox-Rosen, Avi - "One", Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0096)
    - Fox-Rosen, Benjy - "Hot Tear", Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0097)
    - Fraidy Katz - "The Eternal Question", 2006 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0098)
    - Frantic Turtle - "Deformative Moments", Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0099)
    - Freilich, Jonathan, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0100)
    - Friedman, Ilan, 2003 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0101)
    - The Frosen Ox Trio, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0102)
    - Funk's, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0103)
    - Garden State - "Are We Not Jew?", 2004 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0104)
    - Garden State - "Shtetl Fabulous", Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0105)
    - Gelford, Brian, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0106)
    - Gevolt! - "Yiddish Metal", Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0107)
    - Gigi - "Gold and Wax", Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0108)
    - Girls in Trouble - "Instrumental Mix", Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0109)
    - Girls in Trouble - Unmastered, 2009 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0110)
    - Glaser, Sam - "5 Songs for JDub", Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0111)
    - Glass, Seth, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0112)
    - Golan, Rosi, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0113)
    - Goldberg, Sam, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.0114)
    - Golem - "Citizen Boris Mixes", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0115)
    - Golem - demos, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0116)
    - Golem - "Fresh Off Boat" production master 2, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0117)
    - Golem - "Jewltide", 2006 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0322)
    - Golem - mixes, 2006 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0118)
    - Gordon, Rebecka - "Yiddish'n Jazz", 2005 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0119)
    - Great Tap Root - "Animal Magnetism", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0120)
    - Gueoula, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0121)
    - Hajdu, Andre - "The Floating Tower", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0350)
    - Hanukkah Roughs, 2010 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0122)
    - Harvey, Steve - "Oprah", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0123)
    - Haviv, Tamar - "Insatiable", 2001 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0124)
    - Heart Beat Musical, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0125)
    - Hebrew School, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0126)
    - The Hesh Inc., 2006 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0127)
    - Heydemann, Lizzi - "Originals and Jewish Music", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0128)
    - Hidary, Vanessa - "The Hebrew Mamita", 2006 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0129)
    - Himmel, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0130)
    - Hip Hop Khasane, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0131)
    - The Hoodska Explosive - "Tel Aviv", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0132)
    - The Hoodska Explosive - "The Misleading, Session I", 2007 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0133)
    - The Hoodska Explosive - "The Misleading, Session II", 2007 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0134)
    - Incus - "Fire and Bone", 2008 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0135)
    - J. Viewz - "The Besides EP", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0136)
    - Jacobson, Aaron, 2006 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0137)
    - Jacuzzi Project, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0138)
    - Jaded, 2008 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0139)
    - Jafri, Talib - "God Bless", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0140)
    - JDub - "Sampler #1", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0141)
    - Jewdyssee - "Snippet Mix" (copy 1), Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0142)
    - Jewdyssee - "Snippet Mix" (copy 2), Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0143)
    - Jewish Monkeys, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0144)
    - Kahana, Gilad - rough mixes, 2007 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0145)
    - Kahane, Gavriel, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0146)
    - Kapelye, DiNaye, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0147)
    - Karavanah, Divina, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0148)
    - Katz, Noam - "Tofilah" demo, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0149)
    - Katz, Yehuda, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0150)
    - Klar, Marc, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0151)
    - Kogen, Dov - "Numb to Sound", 2005 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0152)
    - Kohane of Newark - "New Midlife Crisis", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0153)
    - Kokolo - "Love International", 2007 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0154)
    - Kraus, Yael - promo cd, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0155)
    - Laible Ben Moshe - "At The Carlebach Shul", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0156)
    - Lane, Yuri - "Human Beatbox, Soundrack City", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0157)
    - Lane, Yuri - New Tracks, 2004 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0158)
    - Larry's "10 Plagues" remix, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0159)
    - Lauri, Robert - "Album Emouna", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0160)
    - Lazarus, Ariel, 2008 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0161)
    - Ledgley, Yehuda - "Passover", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0162)
    - Ledgley, Yehuda - "A View from Here...", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0163)
    - Levitikus, 2007 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0164)
    - Lipman, Paulie - "Inobservant", 2008 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0165)
    - Live at the Walnut Room, Denver CO (1 of 2), 2008 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0166)
    - Live at the Walnut Room, Denver CO (2 of 2), 2008 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0167)
    - Loveman, Michael - "Shalom Brasil", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0168)
    - Lubin, Noah - Unmixed demo, 2007 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0169)
    - Mad Happy, 2009 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0170)
    - Mad Lib - "Bluenote", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0323)
    - Made Men Mixtapes - "A-Typical vol. I", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0171)
    - Manach - "Infinite Bliss" disk 1, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0172)
    - Manach - "Infinite Bliss" disk 2, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0173)
    - Mar, Guy, 2008 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0174)
    - Maroko, Jordan, 2008 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0175)
    - Marsh, S. - "Meditation", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0176)
    - Marty, J. - "Hip Hop", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0177)
    - Marty, J. - "Reggae", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0178)
    - Matisyahu, 2004 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0179)
    - Matisyahu - "AOL Music Sessions", 2006 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0180)
    - Matisyahu - "BB King's Soundboard", 2004 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0181)
    - Matisyahu - "Ben Hesse/Matt Miller", 2002 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0182)
    - Matisyahu - "Dual Disc Revised Final", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0183)
    - Matisyahu - Dubs, 2005 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0184)
    - Matisyahu - Final Master, 2005 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0185)
    - Matisyahu - "Heeb", 2004 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0186)
    - Matisyahu - "Ill Factor", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0187)
    - Matisyahu - "Israel" disk 1, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0188)
    - Matisyahu - "Israel" disk 2, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0189)
    - Matisyahu - "Israel", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0190)
    - Matisyahu - Jewish-American Festival, 2004 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0191)
    - Matisyahu - "Live at The Grog Shop", 2005 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0192)
    - Matisyahu - "Live at Irving Plaza" disk 1, 2005 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0193)
    - Matisyahu - "Live at Irving Plaza" disk 2, 2005 (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0194)
    - Matisyahu - "Live at Stubb's", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0195)
    - Matisyahu - "Live at Stubb's" (burnt copy), Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0196)
    - Matisyahu - "Live at Stubb's" Disk 1, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0197)
    - Matisyahu - "Live at Stubb's" Disk 2, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0198)
    - Matisyahu - "Live at Stubb's" T-Ray portfolio, Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0199)
    - Matisyahu - "Matisyahu Mixtape, DJ Beverly Bonds", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0200)
    - Matisyahu - "Matisyahu Mixtape, from Bev", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0201)
    - Matisyahu - "Matisyahu Mixtape, DJ Beverly Bonds", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0202)
    - Matisyahu - "Old City Beat Box", Undated (Box 31, Disk ID: 330.0203)
    - Matisyahu - "Matisyahu and P.O.D.", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0204)
    - Matisyahu - "Savannah's, Albany" disk 1, 2005 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0205)
    - Matisyahu - "Savannah's, Albany" disk 2, 2005 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0206)
    - Matisyahu - "Shake off the Dust", 2004 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0207)
    - Matisyahu - "Stamp Student Union, U of Maryland", 2004 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0208)
    - Matisyahu - "Trax, Matt Miller", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0209)
    - Matisyahu - "WYPR Baltimore radio", 2004 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0210)
    - Matisyahu - "Youth" final album master, 2005 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0211)
    - MC Aaron, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0212)
    - MC Complete, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0213)
    - Members of the Tribe, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0214)
    - Mens Rea, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0215)
    - Michael Freitberg Quintet - "Harajuku", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0216)
    - Midnight Peacocks - "Shalosh", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0217)
    - Miller, Yonatan - "Jewish Soul", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0218)
    - Morcheeba - "The Antidote", 2005 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0219)
    - Moshav Band - "Shlomo Carlebach", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0220)
    - Moshe, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0221)
    - Moshe's Beats - "5765", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0222)
    - Munach Mix, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0223)
    - Musical Jews - Show # 2 on KZSC, DJ Oy-Dog, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0224)
    - Musical Jews - Show # 3 on KZSC, DJ Oy-Dog, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0225)
    - My Silent Bravery - "Are You Prepared?", 2010 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0226)
    - My Yiddishe Mambo, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0227)
    - The Naked Orchestra, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0228)
    - Nayo, Gilmo - "The Demoe", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0229)
    - Nu Juwish Music - "Live in Paris", 2004 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0230)
    - Onili, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0231)
    - Nu Animal, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0232)
    - Ori, Daniel - "So it Goes" unmastered, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0233)
    - Orion - "Teritorium II", 2005 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0234)
    - Palm - "Fire in You", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0235)
    - Paul, John - "Home Recordings", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0236)
    - Peled Ve Ortega - "Kip On Kickin It", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0237)
    - Persian Mix CD 1, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0238)
    - Pharaoh's Daughter, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0239)
    - PHP - "Jam-Demo", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0240)
    - Playlists - Aaron's playlist, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0241)
    - Playlists - Alicia's playlist, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0242)
    - Playlists - Annette's playlist, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0243)
    - Playlists - Curha's playlist, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0244)
    - Playlists - Taylor's playlist, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0245)
    - Playlists - Tim's playlist, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0246)
    - P.S. 96 Collected Songs - "Hip Hop Math", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0247)
    - Pshemish, Mordichai, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0248)
    - Quilombolas, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0249)
    - Rabbi Abulafia's Boxed Set, 2005 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0250)
    - The Rabbi is Dead, 2011 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0251)
    - Rabbi Rock Music, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0252)
    - Radioyaakov, 2007 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0253)
    - Rakan, 2005 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0254)
    - Ra-Ka-Tak - Red Sea Jazz Fest, 2010 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0255)
    - Ramallah Tel Aviv - master, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0256)
    - Ramallah Tel Aviv - Test, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0257)
    - Ramzailech, 2010 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0258)
    - Razoner - "The Kid Hasid", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0259)
    - Reb Yid - "Songs for the World", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0260)
    - Reboot Stereophonic - "Jewface", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0261)
    - Reuven, Ben - "Sing Jerusalem 3000", 2003 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0262)
    - Reuven, Ben - "Songs", 2007 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0263)
    - Richards, Stephen, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0264)
    - Riddim'tion, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0265)
    - Ridick, Kelli, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0266)
    - Rockinas, Diego - "Yiddish Songs", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0267)
    - Romashka, 2005 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0268)
    - Rooftop III, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0269)
    - Rosen, Brad - "Songs of Spirit", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0270)
    - Rosenblit, David, 2009 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0271)
    - Ross, Tammy - "My Destiny", 2006 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0272)
    - Ross, Tammy - "My Destiny", 2007 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0273)
    - Rothman, Chana, 2005 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0274)
    - Rothman, Chana, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0275)
    - Rubin, Elena - "Sabor a mi Corcovado Hija Mia", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0276)
    - Sagol 59 - Album instrumentals, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0277)
    - Salzberg, Efraim, 2008 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0278)
    - Sandcastle, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0279)
    - Santos, Rutherford P. - "Songs of Devotion", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0280)
    - Sasson - "The Gathering", Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0281)
    - Say Yeah!, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0282)
    - SAZ - demo, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0283)
    - Scatalogics, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0284)
    - Schwartz, Anat, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0285)
    - Serge Keravel, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0286)
    - Serper, Leonora, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0287)
    - Seventh Sunset, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0288)
    - Shakshuka, 2006 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0289)
    - Shank Bone Mystic - "Million Dollar Rock and Roll Carousel", 2005 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0290)
    - Sharvit, Tomer, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0291)
    - Shechter, Adam, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0292)
    - Shmuel, Rav, 2005 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0293)
    - The Shondes, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0294)
    - Showalter, Michael - "[?] Enhancement", 2007 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0295)
    - Showalter, Michael - "Live", 2007 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0296)
    - Showalter, Michael - "At Union Hall" Wed. 1st show, 2007 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0297)
    - Showalter, Michael - "At Union Hall" Wed. 2nd show, 2007 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0298)
    - Showalter, Michael - "At Union Hall" Thu. 1st show, 2007 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0299)
    - Showalter, Michael - "At Union Hall" Thu. 2nd show, 2007 (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0300)
    - The Shtetlblasters, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0301)
    - The Shtetlblasters - "Tantz Mit...", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0351)
    - Shusterman, Vlad, Undated (Box 18, Disk ID: 330.0302)
    - Side by Side - "Practice CD", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0303)
    - Sideways Runners, 2007 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0304)
    - Sneakas, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0305)
    - Sneakas - "In it for the Change", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0306)
    - Sneakas - "Peace in the Middle East Project", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0307)
    - Sneakas and Mazzi, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0308)
    - So Called, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0309)
    - So Called and The Alef Project - "Yiddishkayt Festival", 2004 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0310)
    - So Called, Ben Roughs, Frank London, Biz, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0311)
    - So Called - "Electrohukah EP", 2004 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0312)
    - So Called - "Electrohukah", 2004 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0313)
    - So Called - "The Funkbox", 2005 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0314)
    - So Called - "Ghettoblaster", 2007 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0315)
    - So Called - "Ghettoblaster" rough edit, 2006 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0316)
    - So Called - "Jewltide", 2006 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0317)
    - So Called - "Klez-Funk Hip Hop Maestro", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0318)
    - So Called - "More So Called [Shit], Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0319)
    - So Called - "Montreal Performances", 2003 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0320)
    - So Called - "At the Ottobar, Baltimore", 2006 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0321)
    - Sobol, Marlon L. - "Sojourner", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0324)
    - Soulico - "Album beats", 2007 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0325)
    - Soulico - "Almost There", 2009 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0326)
    - Soulico - "Beats for Album", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0327)
    - Soulico - "Beats from Upcoming JDub Release", 2007 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0328)
    - Soulico - "Digital Monkey Remix Master", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0329)
    - Soulico - DJ Sets, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0330)
    - Soulico - DJ Sets Live on 91.8FM, 2006 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0331)
    - Soulico - "Exotic on the Speaker" May Mix, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0332)
    - Soulico - Final beats, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0333)
    - Soulico - Songs, beats, and instrumentals, CD1, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0334)
    - Soulico - Songs, beats, and instrumentals, CD2, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0335)
    - Soulico - "Three Revised", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0336)
    - Spring Laundromat, 2005 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0337)
    - Stardom - "Ribbon of Love", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0338)
    - Stop Golus, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0339)